[Music]
The whole life, I didn't drink tea.
Then the tea made me awake.
Are you trying to give us more than one?
No, no, no, no.
What was the cure?
A new song for you, Tom.
Interesting hour.
You said you did one day.
I didn't have to do one day.
It is, yes.
He's been hitting on him.
Never had to do anything.
I didn't do anything.
I don't get it, hit it, but I get...
You're not coming to the room?
I don't know, I don't know.
What are you doing?
I don't know.
I'm trying to make it.
Oh, it's a lot of people.
Sometimes I drink it.
I don't know, sometimes I drink it to settle my stomach.
Well, yeah, that's...
What, like, '50s?
It depends on the 'maybe'.
But it's not so bad.
This is, you know, the...
...hard.
...carlin.
...the 'maybe' of you.
No.
I don't really have to work.
I mean, nothing report on what you find.
You know my ankle.
When?
March 26th.
Oh, this time.
No, thank you.
You're interested in the body.
No, you are going here.
Well, the night is coming up.
You know, I'm doing that.
You said that you have to find it to Mr. Romney.
(muffled speaking)
- You see that?
Have the prices down up?
- People stand up.
- There's inflation.
- No, that's not because inflation,
we could have, no one day when you come home,
you just have to have a--
- More happens.
- Okay.
- It's very interesting.
- More service, yeah.
- So this is something.
- Even look for the food.
- You paying too much for entertainment.
- But, you know, I'm going to tell you this is the--
- My poor people.
you have to pay the details.
It comes from 15.
Another one is just liquor.
Let me just have a 50 days because my friend, California,
is the oldest.
You can reckon.
My friends from California are coming tonight.
The left kitchen blood is moldy.
So they might come and see me in tonight, I don't know.
So that'll be most next week.
We'll stay in the same area as we are caught there.
He's getting his family.
So they probably have a spring break or something over there?
I don't know.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Lana from heaven.
This is the best.
This is for you.
No, this one.
This very...
What's back in the family?
I got that corona you told me about.
And when does the next day to deserve it?
It's gone already.
It's gone.
Because I got there 10 times.
At the ninth?
Next day.
It's probably gone.
I didn't walk around.
You want to have these houses around?
(speaking in foreign language)
How many in that?
- How many from there? - Yeah.
- How many? - How many?
- Yeah.
- How can he be king? - He became them.
- He became them. - Very happy.
- Very happy. - They mix up with each other.
- Right.
- Who is this?
- He made it. - Mark?
- He made it so bad.
- I don't think so.
I don't think so.
No.
You're not going to be karma standing in Spain.
I don't believe it.
No, yeah.
This is a day during the address to Franco.
Yeah, I had to...
Even when Franco was first dying,
we still had all this big stamp to them on, you know.
They just changed it.
I know, I don't think so.
And then the money still has in my hand,
and everything.
Oh, thank you.
You're good?
I'm good.
But you want it?
You too, there.
Oh, I will give you 10 times more of this.
I have to like it to be equal for you,
but I have to--
I'm still waiting.
I shall-- I will remember that.
But I have many more for you.
I know that if I give you 100,
you give me 1,000.
No, 200.
[LAUGHTER]
I think I have this.
I must go through here.
So, I wondered the next day to reserve it for you.
What was done? I think you have the full ability.
I think it's very much a decision.
Yes, it's not.
[NON-ENGLISH SPEECH]
I found it quite interesting, though.
In fact, there were some in the way-- there were a few verses.
That's what's interesting about a different translation,
because they approach some verses differently.
It makes you look at them from a different point of view.
[INAUDIBLE]
You know, I'm not...
...fizzling him.
Don't worry.
In that conversation about the translation,
you remember I brought this problem to you about teaching what they didn't know.
Yeah.
I personally am in front of you.
I remember I told you, I don't know if you are...
Yeah.
I don't just put it put it.
But you know what, in my mind, I'll tell you.
Yeah.
Because if these people really know what it means,
it only means that shallot is to the Allah himself.
He just wants something.
I must have had a good reason.
It's kind of Muhammad.
It wouldn't be.
So we can do that with the Quran.
But prayer is taught,
man did not know how to, it's just man's deprecation.
Man did not know how to pray.
It is Allah to talk to him how to pray.
Which strengthens the argument.
No, but I'm not being very peaceful in Poland.
Yeah.
Did you think?
No.
Yes, a lot of people.
But I saw it.
I saw it a lot.
But I didn't want any more because that would be polemical.
You could be coming very disagreeable.
Yeah.
No, it's just...
This last week, I took a call.
I have...
You know, when the events are near, it's very hard to see.
But after a few days, I'm an ally who holds it very well.
In one point of view, it's very difficult.
So maybe in your program, so I'm not going to try it again.
Right, too.
Some allies are going to.
It's very interesting because we have this problem.
In pre-teachies.
From a new club population.
Yeah, you go ahead. I'll give them an eye.
Go ahead, I'll give them an eye.
See it tonight, before I go.
You're looking like there is a family.
I mean, from Angeles, all the way from the English to this evening, they left at 6 o'clock.
What time are they supposed to come?
12 hours.
Too much.
But maybe they will be tired.
If they are too tired, they will not come.
They are the same person I met.
They come here.
Big man.
They have been in the town in the studio.
Anyhow, are you still recording for me?
No, are you still recording for me?
No, I'm not.
Oh, it's like I'm done.
The police are from all...
Assertion.
Yeah.
Assertion is power, again.
The contagion of even.
From...
It's none of those boys are beating themselves.
It's not interested in A or not A or BZ.
And he got to make fishing in front.
Now tell him how.
If he plays a very current game,
if he plays a very current game, he can take off a collision.
Because he's a man looking for identity.
And he's going to do what he's called.
And then, he only made a widget in a firewall.
He's like, "Oh, you need to go to the rest of the tower."
He's pushing.
So they're using him.
And he's using him.
He's using him to get monetary growth.
But really, I think we're seeing one minute or whatever.
Do you think we have a vote on?
Do you think we should show how smart do you?
- You know what they are?
- For men.
- If they are--
- For men is the worst.
- We're not saying about climate.
- Well, would they ever come again?
I think we should set it up formally.
I know I'm being recorded and I give myself the list.
I'm a reporter.
You know, we have a media--
have written questions submitted.
I have the media speak the question and then...
The camera.
What I was hoping they would have done in the first place and what is what it debate is.
That wasn't the debate.
It's an intelligent discussion between people.
From the beginning, the picture.
The picture.